Technical University of British Columbia fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Office of the President records, 1986 - 2002; F-177-1; 8.65 m of textual records and other material; Dates of creation: Predominant dates of the series are 1995-2002. Physical description: Includes 46 photographs, 3 contact sheets, 14 videocassettes, 3 audio cassettes, 1 compact disk, and 2 artifa
  - President's historical files, 1993 - 2001; F-177-1-16; 92 cm of textual records 42 photographs 3 contact sheets 1 compact disk
    Sub-series consists of records selected by the President as historically significant to TechBC. Activities, events and topics documented include activities of the Interim Planning Council and the Interim Governing Board; the dispute over tenure with the Canadian Association of University Teachers (CAUT); historical milestones in the development of the University; the determination of its location; partnerships formed with private corporations, post-secondary institutions, and other organizations; the search for the first President and CEO; Executive, staff and other meetings; presentations and talks given by the President to external groups; Core Services Review of TechBC; and the University's participation in the BC High Technology Strategy. Records include correspondence; reports; minutes; booklets, brochures, promotional material, newspaper articles, and press releases; academic calendars; presentations; financial records; lists; photographs; compact disk; and legislation.
    Technical University of British Columbia. Interim Planning Council.; Technical University of British Columbia. Interim Governing Board; Fraser Valley University Society
    - [Virtual tour of TechBC campus at Central City], 2000; F-177-1-16-0-0-1 (Optical disc: cd OBJ-2424)
      Moving images
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-177-item20.
    - BC High Technology Strategy meeting minutes and supporting documents, vol. 1, June 1998 - June 1999; F-177-1-16-0-1 (Archival box - standard 177-48)
    - BC High Technology Strategy meeting minutes and supporting documents, vol. 2, June 1998 - June 1999; F-177-1-16-0-2 (Archival box - standard 177-48)
    - BC High Technology Strategy Working Group meetings, August 1998 - February 1999; F-177-1-16-0-3 (Archival box - standard 177-48)
    - Grading Workflow Project brief package, 2001; F-177-1-16-0-4 (Archival box - standard 177-48)
    - The Office of VP, Research and External Affairs, 2001; F-177-1-16-0-5 (Archival box - standard 177-48)
    - Technical University of BC Act and related statutes, vol. 1, 1998 - 1999; F-177-1-16-0-6 (Archival box - standard 177-49)
    - Technical University of BC Act and related statutes, vol. 2, 1998 - 1999; F-177-1-16-0-7 (Archival box - standard 177-49)
    - Comparison of alternate university legislation, vol. 1, 1997; F-177-1-16-0-8 (Archival box - standard 177-49)
    - Comparison of alternate university legislation, vol. 2, 1997; F-177-1-16-0-9 (Archival box - standard 177-49)
    - Comparison of alternate university legislation, vol. 3, 1997; F-177-1-16-0-10 (Archival box - standard 177-49)
    - CAUT boycott, vol. 1, 1997 - 1998; F-177-1-16-0-11 (Archival box - standard 177-49)
    - CAUT boycott, vol. 2, 1997 - 1998; F-177-1-16-0-12 (Archival box - standard 177-49)
    - CAUT boycott, vol. 3, 1997 - 1998; F-177-1-16-0-13 (Archival box - standard 177-49)
    - CAUT boycott, vol. 4, 1997 - 1998; F-177-1-16-0-14 (Archival box - standard 177-50)
    - Report: In step with the future - supporting Infinite Possibilities, 1998; F-177-1-16-0-15 (Archival box - standard 177-50)
    - Report: Post-secondary education in the Okanagan, July 2000; F-177-1-16-0-16 (Archival box - standard 177-50)
    - Agenda - meeting with Tom Calvert, 20 November 1997; F-177-1-16-0-17 (Archival box - standard 177-50)
    - Report: Technical University of British Columbia: A Work in Progress, 1998; F-177-1-16-0-18 (Archival box - standard 177-50)
    - Press releases, vol. 1, 1996 - 1997; F-177-1-16-0-19 (Archival box - standard 177-50)
    - Brochure: TechBC: Centre for Electronic Commerce, 1999; F-177-1-16-0-20 (Archival box - standard 177-50)
    - Brochure: TechBC: graduate programs, 1999; F-177-1-16-0-21 (Archival box - standard 177-50)
    - Brochure: TechBC Corporation: Infinite Possiblities in Partnership, 1999; F-177-1-16-0-22 (Archival box - standard 177-50)
    - Brochure: Surrey City Centre, 2000; F-177-1-16-0-23 (Archival box - standard 177-50)
    - TechBC calendar 1999/2000, F-177-1-16-0-24 (Archival box - standard 177-50)
    - Report: Financial Review of TechBC, 19 October 2000; F-177-1-16-0-25 (Archival box - standard 177-50)
    - TechBC Course Outlines: 1999/2000 Academic Year, vol. 1, 18 April 2000; F-177-1-16-0-26 (Archival box - standard 177-50)
    - Report: Academic Plan Information (draft), 31 July 1998; F-177-1-16-0-27 (Archival box - standard 177-50)
    - Invoices for house space lease, Jean Watters, 2001; F-177-1-16-0-28 (Archival box - standard 177-50)
    - Core review process, vol. 1, 2001; F-177-1-16-0-29 (Archival box - standard 177-51)
    - Core review process, vol. 2, 2001; F-177-1-16-0-30 (Archival box - standard 177-51)
    - Core review process, vol. 3, 2001; F-177-1-16-0-31 (Archival box - standard 177-51)
    - Core review process, vol. 4, 2001; F-177-1-16-0-32 (Archival box - standard 177-51)
    - Core review process, vol. 5, 2001; F-177-1-16-0-33 (Archival box - standard 177-51)
    - TechBC showcase, vol. 1, 10 October 2001; F-177-1-16-0-34 (Archival box - standard 177-51)
    - TechBC showcase, vol. 2, 10 October 2001; F-177-1-16-0-35 (Archival box - standard 177-51)
    - Political history and milestones of TechBC, 1999/08/17, 1530-1700 hours, The Bridge, 1998 - 2000; F-177-1-16-0-36 (Archival box - standard 177-51)
    - President's Office, vol. 1, 1996 - 2000; F-177-1-16-0-37 (Archival box - standard 177-51)
    - Milestones, 1997 - 2001; F-177-1-16-0-38 (Archival box - standard 177-51)
    - [ICBC proposal], 1998; F-177-1-16-0-39 (Archival box - standard 177-51)
    - Brochures: Central City / Focus on the Future: Surrey City Centre, 2000; F-177-1-16-0-40 (Archival box - standard 177-51)
    - LG Semicon, 1997; F-177-1-16-0-41 (Archival box - standard 177-51)
    - Site announcement: July 20, 1998 (Surrey City Hall), F-177-1-16-0-42 (Archival box - standard 177-51)
    - Site announcement: July 20, 1998 (Surrey City Hall) (photographs), 20 July 1998; F-177-1-16-0-43 (Archival box - small 177-68)
    - Community relations - HSSRC, vol. 1, 1996 - 1997; F-177-1-16-0-44 (Archival box - standard 177-52)
    - Community relations - HSSRC, vol. 2, 1996 - 1997; F-177-1-16-0-45 (Archival box - standard 177-52)
    - Small histories: SFU, BCIT, colleges, FVUS, 1997; F-177-1-16-0-46 (Archival box - standard 177-52)
    - Foundation for Innovation, vol. 1, 1997; F-177-1-16-0-47 (Archival box - standard 177-52)
    - Foundation for Innovation, vol. 2, 1997; F-177-1-16-0-48 (Archival box - standard 177-52)
    - Sony, 1997; F-177-1-16-0-49 (Archival box - standard 177-52)
    - Motorola, vol. 1, 1997; F-177-1-16-0-50 (Archival box - standard 177-52)
    - Motorola, vol. 2, 1997; F-177-1-16-0-51 (Archival box - standard 177-52)
    - Motorola, vol. 3, 1997; F-177-1-16-0-52 (Archival box - standard 177-52)
    - [COOL Meeting (Co-ordination in Learning)], 1998; F-177-1-16-0-53 (Archival box - standard 177-52)
    - Management Group meetings, 1997; F-177-1-16-0-54 (Archival box - standard 177-52)
    - Executive Group meeting, 16 October 1997; F-177-1-16-0-55 (Archival box - standard 177-52)
    - Interim Governing Board and staff meetings, November 1995 - January 1996; F-177-1-16-0-56 (Archival box - standard 177-52)
    - Printed projections for Interim Planning [Council], 1996; F-177-1-16-0-57 (Archival box - standard 177-53)
    - Staff meetings, vol. 1, July 1996 - September 1996; F-177-1-16-0-58 (Archival box - standard 177-53)
    - Staff meetings, vol. 1, October 1996 - November 1996; F-177-1-16-0-59 (Archival box - standard 177-53)
    - Staff meetings, vol. 1, 1997; F-177-1-16-0-60 (Archival box - standard 177-53)
    - Alliance - general, 1997 - 1998; F-177-1-16-0-61 (Archival box - standard 177-53)
    - Alliance, vol. 1, 1997 - 1998; F-177-1-16-0-62 (Archival box - standard 177-53)
    - Alliance notes, 1997; F-177-1-16-0-63 (Archival box - standard 177-53)
    - Presentations: APEGBC (Association of Professional Engineers and Geoscientists of BC), 1997; F-177-1-16-0-64 (Archival box - standard 177-53)
    - Presentations: BCIT, 1996; F-177-1-16-0-65 (Archival box - standard 177-53)
    - Presentations: BCTel/City of Surrey, 1997; F-177-1-16-0-66 (Archival box - standard 177-53)
    - Presentations: Caldwell, 1996; F-177-1-16-0-67 (Archival box - standard 177-53)
    - Presentations: CAUT, 1997; F-177-1-16-0-68 (Archival box - standard 177-53)
    - CEO breakfast, 25 September 1998; F-177-1-16-0-69 (Archival box - standard 177-53)
    - Presentations: Cougar Canyon Elementary PAC, 1/28/1997, F-177-1-16-0-70 (Archival box - standard 177-53)
    - Presentations: Pacific Association of Continuing Education, 11/16/1998, F-177-1-16-0-71 (Archival box - standard 177-53)
    - Presentations: Science Council, 10/23/1998, F-177-1-16-0-72 (Archival box - standard 177-53)
    - Presentations: Sonoma State University, 10/17/1996, F-177-1-16-0-73 (Archival box - standard 177-53)
    - Presentations: UBC/Green College, 9/26/1996, F-177-1-16-0-74 (Archival box - standard 177-53)
    - New technical university announcement - photo contact sheets, February 1995; F-177-1-16-0-75 (Archival box - small 177-68)
    - Technical University of British Columbia Interim Planning Council: Preliminary report to Ministry of Education, Skills and Training (draft), vol. 1, June 1996; F-177-1-16-0-76 (Archival box - standard 177-54)
    - Real and Virtual Estate: Keys to TechBC [Power point presentation], 1997; F-177-1-16-0-77 (Archival box - standard 177-54)
    - Report: TechBC: Five Year Capital Plan and 2001/02 Capital Budget, 2000; F-177-1-16-0-78 (Archival box - standard 177-54)
    - Scholarships, vol. 1, 1996; F-177-1-16-0-79 (Archival box - standard 177-54)
    - Scholarships [photograph], 1996; F-177-1-16-0-80 (Archival box - small 177-68)
    - Report: Technical University of British Columbia - Current Planning Directions, 7 September 2000; F-177-1-16-0-81 (Archival box - standard 177-54)
    - Interim Planning Council: meetings - back-up material, 1995 - 1996; F-177-1-16-0-82 (Archival box - standard 177-54)
    - Interim Planning Council: CEO - search firm, 1995; F-177-1-16-0-83 (Archival box - standard 177-54)
    - Interim Planning Council: CEO - advertising, 1995; F-177-1-16-0-84 (Archival box - standard 177-54)
    - Interim Planning Council: [Meeting] - December 11, 1995, F-177-1-16-0-85 (Archival box - standard 177-54)
    - Interim Planning Council: [Meeting] - November 25, 1995, F-177-1-16-0-86 (Archival box - standard 177-54)
    - Interim Planning Council: [Meeting] - November 14, 1995, F-177-1-16-0-87 (Archival box - standard 177-54)
    - Interim Planning Council: [Meeting] - October 28, 1995, F-177-1-16-0-88 (Archival box - standard 177-54)
    - Interim Planning Council: [Meeting] - October 16, 1995, F-177-1-16-0-89 (Archival box - standard 177-54)
    - Interim Planning Council: [Meeting] - September 30, 1995, F-177-1-16-0-90 (Archival box - standard 177-54)
    - Interim Planning Council: Meeting - September 18, 1995, F-177-1-16-0-91 (Archival box - standard 177-54)
    - Interim Planning Council: Meeting - September 5, 1995, F-177-1-16-0-92 (Archival box - standard 177-54)
    - Interim Planning Council: Meeting - August 21, 1995, F-177-1-16-0-93 (Archival box - standard 177-54)
    - Interim Planning Council: Meeting - August 8, 1995, 1993 - 1995; F-177-1-16-0-94 (Archival box - standard 177-54)
    - Interim Planning Council: Meeting - July 24, 1995, F-177-1-16-0-95 (Archival box - standard 177-54)
    - Interim Planning Council: Meeting - July 8, 1995, F-177-1-16-0-96 (Archival box - standard 177-54)
    - Interim Planning Council: Meeting - June 26, 1995, KUC Surrey Campus, F-177-1-16-0-97 (Archival box - standard 177-54)
    - Interim Planning Council: Meeting - June 10, 1995, KUC Langley Campus, F-177-1-16-0-98 (Archival box - standard 177-54)
    - Interim Planning Council: [Meeting] - June 6, 1996, F-177-1-16-0-99 (Archival box - standard 177-54)
    - Interim Planning Council: [Meeting] - May 2, 1996, F-177-1-16-0-100 (Archival box - standard 177-54)
    - Interim Planning Council: [Meeting] - April 10, 1996, F-177-1-16-0-101 (Archival box - standard 177-55)
    - Interim Planning Council: [Meeting] - March 7, 1996, F-177-1-16-0-102 (Archival box - standard 177-55)
    - Interim Planning Council: [Meeting] - February 17, 1996, F-177-1-16-0-103 (Archival box - standard 177-55)
    - Interim Planning Council: [Meeting] - February 8, 1996, F-177-1-16-0-104 (Archival box - standard 177-55)
    - Interim Planning Council: [Meeting] - January 11, 1996, 1995 - 1996; F-177-1-16-0-105 (Archival box - standard 177-55)
    - Interim Planning Council - photographs - members, vol. 1, 1996; F-177-1-16-0-106 (Archival box - standard 177-55)
    - Interim Planning Council - photographs - members, vol. 2, 1996; F-177-1-16-0-107 (Archival box - small 177-68)
    - Interim Governing Board - Society Act, vol. 1, 1995 - 1997; F-177-1-16-0-108 (Archival box - standard 177-55)
    - Interim Governing Board - Society Act, vol. 2, 1995 - 1997; F-177-1-16-0-109 (Archival box - standard 177-55)
    - Interim Governing Board - Society Act, vol. 3, 1995 - 1997; F-177-1-16-0-110 (Archival box - standard 177-55)
    - Interim Governing Board - Society Act, vol. 4, 1995 - 1997; F-177-1-16-0-111 (Archival box - standard 177-55)
  - TechBC historical files, 1988 - 2002; F-177-1-17; Analog originals 1.15 m of textual records 10 moving images (12 videocassettes) 3 sound recordings (3 audiocassettes) 2 artifacts Digitized materials: Preservation copies - 11 mov files (201.95 GB); 4 wav files (3.38 GB) Access copies - 11 mp4 files (7.85 GB); 4 mp3 files (133.5 MB)
    Sub-series consists of records maintained by the Office of the President for historical purposes. Activities, events and topics documented include the establishment and development of TechBC; the Fraser Valley University Society's role in the creation of TechBC; opening of the University; the political and educational climate surrounding the University's development; the President's daily activities; program and services development; funding; and television and radio interviews. Records include Internal Planning Reports produced in 1996 and 1997 to facilitate the planning of the University. Records include reports and proposals; correspondence; brochures; calendars; minutes and agendas; presentations; course outlines; working papers; notes; day calendar; certificate of incorporation; and videocassettes, audiocassettes, and artifacts.
    Analog originals were digitized by the Archives in 2018. Digitial copies are available in mp4 or mp3 (access format), and mov or wav (preservation format). Please contact the reference archivist to request copies.
    - FVUS Master, 1994; F-177-1-17-0-0-1 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2425)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-177-item12.
    - Public Forum: Fraser Valley University Society, 1994; F-177-1-17-0-0-2 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2426)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-177-item13.
    - FVUS - Public Relations Video, Fall 1994 (Shilliday copy), F-177-1-17-0-0-3 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2428)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-177-item14.
    - FVUS Forum, Delta Cable TV, April 30, 1994; F-177-1-17-0-0-4 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2427)
      Delta Cable TV; Moving images
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-177-item11.
    - TechBC / CBC Interview, 1997; F-177-1-17-0-0-5 (Audio cassette OBJ-3264)
      Canadian Broadcasting Corporation; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-177-item17.
    - CBC Early Edition: Robert Clift / Ron Dixon on TechBC, Host: Catherine Gretsinger, 28 July 1997; F-177-1-17-0-0-6 (Audio cassette OBJ-3263)
      Canadian Broadcasting Corporation; Clift, Robert; Ron Dixon; Gretsinger, Catherine; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-177-item16.
    - The Bill Good Show: TechBC, 27 August 1997; F-177-1-17-0-0-7 (Audio cassette OBJ-3262)
      Good, Bill; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-177-item15.
    - Bernie's interview on Cable 4, 1999; F-177-1-17-0-0-8 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2429)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-177-item3.
    - The New Partnership: Managing for Excellence, 1999; F-177-1-17-0-0-9 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2430)
      Tape is damaged.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-177-item4.
    - TechBC Opening Day, October 18, 1999; F-177-1-17-0-0-10 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2431)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-177-item7.
    - Rough cut - working master, [1992]; F-177-1-17-0-0-11 (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2432, Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2433, Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2434)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-177-item8.
    - Award: 2000 BC Innovation Awards in Educational Technology Bright and Shiny Award - Educational Technology and Learning Team Tech BC, F-177-1-17-0-0-12 (Archival box - small 177-67)
      Artefacts
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-177-item18.
    - Award: "In recognition of your contributions in establishing the Technical University of British Columbia", 5 February 2001; F-177-1-17-0-0-13 (Archival box - small 177-67)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-177-item19.
    - Legislative Channel: Open Cabinet Meeting - Nick Geer, CEO ICBC; TechBC, November 7, 2001; F-177-1-17-0-0-14; 1 videocassette 1 .mov file (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2435)
      Legislative Channel
      07 Nov 01, 9:00 PT
      re: open cabinet meeting
      -Nick Geer, CEO ICBC
      -Tech BC
      1. Nick Geer 04 min
      2. Greg Halsey-Brandt, 02m 30s
      3. Gulzar Cheema, 02m
      Geer, Nick; Moving images; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-177-item6.
    - CIVT-TV: No Government Funding for TechBC, November 21, 2001; F-177-1-17-0-0-15; 1 videocassette 1 .mov file (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2436)
      21 Nov. 01, CIVT-TV, 18:12, B. Good/P. Martin, 1:30 m
      Re: No Government Funding for Tech BC
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-177-item5.
    - Historical document I, 1-02: Access to Advanced Education and Job Training in British Columbia, 1988; F-177-1-17-0-1 (Archival box - standard 177-55)
    - Historical document I, 1-03: Report of the Fraser Valley Planning Committee, September 1989; F-177-1-17-0-2 (Archival box - standard 177-55)
    - Historical document I, 1-04: Demographic Survey of the Lower Mainland of British Columbia, 1989; F-177-1-17-0-3 (Archival box - standard 177-56)
    - Historical document I, 1-05: Findings of the Fraser Valley Access Committee: Summary and Recommendations, December 1989; F-177-1-17-0-4 (Archival box - standard 177-56)
    - Historical document I, 1-06: Findings of the Fraser Valley Access Committee: A Report, December 1989; F-177-1-17-0-5 (Archival box - standard 177-56)
    - Historical document I, 1-07: Findings of the Fraser Valley Access Committee: A Report, June 1990; F-177-1-17-0-6 (Archival box - standard 177-56)
    - Historical document I, 1-08: University College of the Fraser Valley, September 1990; F-177-1-17-0-7 (Archival box - standard 177-56)
    - Historical document I, 1-09: Simon Fraser University Submission to the Fraser Valley Access Consultation Group, September 1990; F-177-1-17-0-8 (Archival box - standard 177-56)
    - Historical document I, 1-10: Langley: Home of the Next Provincial University in the Fraser Valley, 1 October 1990; F-177-1-17-0-9 (Archival box - standard 177-56)
    - Historical document I, 1-11: 1990 Environmental Scan, F-177-1-17-0-10 (Archival box - standard 177-56)
    - Historical document I, 1-12: After High School - What?? The Public's Response to Findings of Fraser Valley Access Committee, February 1991; F-177-1-17-0-11 (Archival box - standard 177-56)
    - Historical document I, 1-13: Technical University of British Columbia: a proposal for the new university to be located in the Fraser Valley, October 1991; F-177-1-17-0-12 (Archival box - standard 177-56)
    - Historical document I, 1-14: Advanced Education Council of British Columbia: Access for Equity and Opportunity…, August 1992; F-177-1-17-0-13 (Archival box - standard 177-56)
    - Historical document I, 1-15: Open College Planning Council: Labour Trends and Training Needs in British Columbia, 1992; F-177-1-17-0-14 (Archival box - standard 177-56)
    - Historical document I, 1-16: Preparing for the Future: A University in Surrey/White Rock, January 1993; F-177-1-17-0-15 (Archival box - standard 177-56)
    - Historical document I, 1-17: Fraser Valley University Society: Educational Demographics of the Fraser Valley Region, February 1993; F-177-1-17-0-16 (Archival box - standard 177-56)
    - Historical document I, 1-18: Report of the Committee on Governance in Colleges and Institutes: Recommendations for Revised Governance Structures, May 1993; F-177-1-17-0-17 (Archival box - standard 177-56)
    - Historical document I, 1-19: Report of the Fraser Valley Committee on Post-Secondary Education: Phase 1, June 1993; F-177-1-17-0-18 (Archival box - standard 177-56)
    - Historical document I, 1-20: Social Investment in R and D: Universities and the Obstacles to Knowledge Transfer, August 1994; F-177-1-17-0-19 (Archival box - standard 177-56)
    - Participation rate, student tracking [reports]: Life Trajectories, Action, and Negotiating the Transition from High School, 1991; F-177-1-17-0-20 (Archival box - standard 177-57)
    - Participation rate, student tracking [reports]: History of FTE's1990/91 to 1993/94, November 1994; F-177-1-17-0-21 (Archival box - standard 177-57)
    - Participation rate, student tracking [reports]: Class of 1988, Grade 12 follow-up. Five years later…, February 1995; F-177-1-17-0-22 (Archival box - standard 177-57)
    - Participation rate, student tracking [reports]: Transition Context and Trends, 1996; F-177-1-17-0-23 (Archival box - standard 177-57)
    - Participation rate, student tracking [reports]: Every Indicator tells a Story…, January 1996; F-177-1-17-0-24 (Archival box - standard 177-57)
    - Participation rate, student tracking [reports]: Ministry of Skills, Training and Labour: Environmental Scan, February 1996; F-177-1-17-0-25 (Archival box - standard 177-57)
    - Participation rate, student tracking [reports]: BCCAT Special Report: Beyond Secondary School Graduation, April 1996 - April 1996; F-177-1-17-0-26 (Archival box - standard 177-57)
    - Participation rate, student tracking [reports]: Demographic, Educational, and Occupational Profiles of 1988 High School Graduates within the Catchment Area..., October 1996; F-177-1-17-0-27 (Archival box - standard 177-57)
    - Participation rate, student tracking [reports]: Secondary to Post Secondary Transition Review Project - Information Package for Transition Review Team, first meeting, 11 October 1996; F-177-1-17-0-28 (Archival box - standard 177-57)
    - Participation rate, student tracking [reports]: Technical University of British Columbia Local Industry Needs Analysis, November 1996; F-177-1-17-0-29 (Archival box - standard 177-57)